The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Let's play chase !
Wan'er,
I will wait for you to be reborn.
6 months later
Push !
Come on !
I see it.
Harder !
Awesome !
Congratulations, Mister Zhou.
It's a girl.
Mother and daughter are safe.
But the kid's body
is very weak.
You'll have to take care of her.
Definitely. Definitely.
Thank you.
Come on in.
Zhou Ru
It worked.
Given how weak Wan'er's Nascent Soul is,
it will take about 18 years for her to wake up
and recover her memory.
At that time,
the law of the heavens will surely come again...
Wan'er,
I will protect you.
1 year later
Senior,
Going through Chu is the easiest way to reach the Immortal Graveyard.
Then it's up to Senior.
I haven't come to Chu in 100 years.
There seems to be many changes.
Yes it has,
I heard that nowadays the Cloud Sky Sect
is the number one sect in Chu.
It's not what it used to be.
A messenger from Suzaku ?
What is he doing here ?
Fellow cultivator Ceng Niu,
Mount Suzaku ordered
that in 3 months,
in the western Heaven Temple,
you are to fight Red Butterfly.
What ?
Ceng Niu ?
Go back and tell them
that if they want a fight
it will have to be in 10 years.
This Ceng Niu is really something.
He doesn't even give in to the country of Suzaku.
Old friends in the valley,
please come in.
Old friends ?
Wang Lin ?!
It's him !
Fellow cultivators,
please sit.
I don't know if I should call you fellow cultivator Wang
or fellow cultivator Ceng.
Names are just what we call each other.
There is no need to worry too much about it.
Back then,
I didn't know Senior's identity.
I hope Senior can forgive my rudeness.
If I understand correctly
you're going to the Immortal Graveyard
to find your father's body.
Exactly.
Brother Wang,
why don't you come with us ?
Why did you agree to go, fellow cultivator Sun ?
Senior,
inside the Immortal Graveyard there's a relic
named the Reincarnation Tree.
Junior has a map that can lead us there.
If you meditate under it,
you can experience a life cycle, it's useful for Soul Formation domains.
This may be helpful for Nascent Soul cultivators
but for those above the middle stage of Soul Formation
the effects are minimal.
I believe fellow cultivator Sun has other goals for this trip.
Brother Wang is very insightful,
I'm impressed.
Fellow cultivator Zi Xin, don't blame me.
If it was just for the Reincarnation Tree,
I wouldn't follow you there.
What I want
is the Reincarnation Fruit.
the Reincarnation Fruit ?
That's right !
The Reincarnation Fruit
will increase one's chance of reaching Soul Transformation by 30%.
It's a treasure for us Soul Formation cultivators.
If Brother Wang is willing to go
harvest Reincarnation Fruits,
we will split them evenly.
How does it sound ?
If they're so precious,
why don't you just keep them for yourself
instead of asking me for help ?
Brother Wang doesn't know
but the Immortal Graveyard
is a very dangerous place.
Entrance of the\NImmortal Graveyard
It's the home of powerful native savages.
Even the country of Suzaku dreads them.
If Brother Wang accompanies me,
this trip will be much safer.
As long as we find the Reincarnation Tree,
I have a method for it to bear fruit
within 3 hours.
Interested now ?
How about this:
we will wait for you outside the Immortal Graveyard for 1 month.
If you don’t come,
it's alright.
We will go on our own.
See you.
Tu Si's memory mentioned the Reincarnation Fruit.
If smeared over an Ancient God's body
it will cleanse the meridians
and merge with the flesh and blood.
The speed at which the body absorbs energy
will increase significantly.
This process
is called body cleansing.
Only through body cleansing
can one be regarded as a true Ancient God.
Red Butterfly's residence\NCountry of Suzaku
The Elders were furious because Ceng Niu postponed the battle.
I wanted to go down there to catch him myself
but these guys stopped me again.
I don't even know who this Ceng Niu is.
I can't believe they intervened 3 times already.
Junior Sister,
why don't I sneak down the mountain and kill him for you ?
Even if they find out
they will only punish me to 100 years of secluded cultivation.
Stay here Senior Brother.
Ceng Niu wanted to destroy my Dao Heart
but he never thought that
not only was it not destroyed,
but it's even more complete now.
I don't know what the intentions of Mount Suzaku are
regarding our upcoming battle.
But this is exactly what I want.
Junior Sister,
Spirit of the Eastern Sea
This is the Spirit of the Eastern Sea that I've found,
it will regrow your arm.
Please take it.
I don't need it.
Every time I look at my empty sleeve,
my urge to kill Ceng Niu increases.
Until I kill Ceng Niu,
my arm will stay missing.
Junior Sister !
He's using my arm
to curse me.
Ceng Niu...
I'm definitely going to kill you !
One more poison curse,
just in case she shows up.
The country of Suzaku knows where I'm hiding.
but they didn't tell Red Butterfly
and only sent a challenge letter.
This is weird.
This battle with Red Butterfly is inevitable
so I'd better get ready.
I'm taking back the Beast Trap
to use for this beast.
If you wish to stay, then follow me.
If you don’t, then you may leave.
Capture !
Restrain !
So you thought about it
and you're following me ?
Look at her.
You've had a busy day,
go get something to eat.
Come, dinner's waiting for you.
Wan'er...
in 18 years
you will remember everything about us.
That's when
the law of the heavens will come again.
I must be prepared
to face it again.
The Immortal Graveyard can help me raise my cultivation.
So even if it's dangerous,
I still have to go.
While I'm gone,
you will take care of Wan'er.
Without fail.
Sure.
You have the talent
and you're hard-working.
Keep it up,
I'm sure you will reach Soul Formation.
This is for you,
study it well.
Thank you, Ancestor.
Look at this.
Little Ru, look !
I'll come back for you.
Wait for me.
Senior,
Junior Wang Lin
promised Senior Zhou Yi
to take care of you for 1000 years.
Right now,
Junior will go to the Immortal Graveyard.
It's a very dangerous place
so I would like to borrow a sword.
The Sword Spirit
is gone.
If I want to use it,
I will need a Sword Spirit.
Xu Liguo,
come out.
I'm finally out !
Even if I'm your slave, you could treat me better.
With a devil as the Sword Spirit,
I can only utilize a fraction of the sword's power.
When I get the chance,
I must look for a more suitable Sword Spirit.
Senior Sun,
it has been a month.
Why are we still waiting ?
Do you know how many floors there are in this place ?
I don't.
But my father said before
that this place is relatively safe above the fourth floor.
The lower you go, the more dangerous it gets.
And I'm certain that
the Reincarnation Tree is on the third floor.
My father saw it with his own eyes.
Including Brother Wang,
with 3 Soul Formation cultivators,
as long as we avoid the fourth floor,
it should be safe.
But if he doesn't come...
Brother Wang !
Sorry for the wait.
I had some minor trouble along the way.
I found this person following me
after I entered the Immortal Graveyard.
He was trying to ambush me.
Is he one of the native savages ?
Impossible,
the savages cannot leave the underground.
How did he end up here ?
I'm afraid there's something going on in the Immortal Graveyard.
We have to hurry,
I'll clear the way.
Immortal Graveyard\NFirst floor
The entrance to the second floor is east of here.
This place is huge.
I can't scan it all with my Divine Sense.
Tattoo puppets\NImmortal Graveyard
Senior, help me !
The skulls of these men
are same as what you found above ground.
But
none of them were savages.
What are they ?
Tattoo puppets.
So it's just regular puppets ?
It is said that the real savages
can turn a cultivator into a puppet.
The characteristic of these puppets
are these tattoo
and red eyes.
But these tattoo puppets are not as powerful as a real savages.
You don't usually run into them until the second floor.
I don't know why they're here.
This leaf on the head of the puppet,
what does it mean ?
Miss ?
Lady Zi Xin,
are you okay ?
It's fine,
the entrance is just ahead.
Miss, be careful.
Forsaken Immortal Clan\N3-leaf Shaman
A real savage
with Nascent Soul cultivation !
(Forsaken Immortal Clan's language) Invaders,
you are all
going to die !
Why are there such savages
in planet Suzaku's underground ?
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.